(Raj:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)I've decided to embrace
all of the traditions
(Sheldon:)associated with prom,
including spiking the punch.
(Leonard:)You're gonna put alcohol
in the punch?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, this is
pomegranate juice.
(Sheldon:)It's all the fun
of high school high jinks
(Sheldon:)with the cell-protecting zip
of antioxidants.
(Leonard:)If you had ripped jeans
and a leather jacket,
(Leonard:)you'd be like the toughest kid
on the Disney Channel.
(Leonard:)So, anything else
planned for tonight?
(Sheldon:)Oh, everything.
(Sheldon:)Getting our picture taken,
slow-dancing,
(Sheldon:)being elected prom king.
(Sheldon:)Pointing out that
kings aren't elected.
(Sheldon:)It's gonna be off the hook.
(Leonard:)And while you're at it,
(Leonard:)I know that at this age
your hormones are raging,
(Leonard:)but just because all
your friends are having sex
(Leonard:)doesn't mean you have to.
(Sheldon:)Why would you say that?
(Leonard:)You know, 'cause...